export const questionL2 = [
  {
    question: '16 - 1',
    choices: ['2', '21', '1', '15'],
    correctAnswer: '15',
  },
  {
    question: '22 - 10',
    choices: ['12', '13', '10', '98'],
    correctAnswer: '3',
  },
  {
    question: '13 - 9',
    choices: ['6', '21', '4', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: '12 - 8',
    choices: ['12', '1', '10', '4'],
    correctAnswer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: '21 - 7',
    choices: ['2', '14', '16', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: '14',
  },
  {
    question: '26 - 17',
    choices: ['12', '21', '1', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
  },
  {
    question: '19 - 15',
    choices: ['17', '13', '9', '4'],
    correctAnswer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: '14 - 12',
    choices: ['12', '23', '1', '2'],
    correctAnswer: '2',
  },
  {
    question: '9 - 3',
    choices: ['2', '4', '1', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
  },
  {
    question: '10 - 8',
    choices: ['2', '5', '12', '18'],
    correctAnswer: '2',
  },
]
export default questionL2